<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bongio's reflections on Bongio's blog</title><link>https://bongio.me/</link><description>Recent content in Bongio's reflections on Bongio's blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Copyright © 2023 - 2025 Paolo Ferdinando Bongiovanni.</copyright><atom:link href="https://bongio.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A ghost project - Debate visual language</title><link>https://bongio.me/blog/thinking/debate_visual_lanugage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bongio.me/blog/thinking/debate_visual_lanugage/</guid><description>&lt;p>A few years ago, the UK voted to leave the European Union. Since then, the UK left the EU.
Before the vote, there was a lot of emotion surrounding the debate about whether one should vote to stay or leave. I witnessed the discussion but couldn&amp;rsquo;t express my opinion during the vote as an EU citizen.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Looking for Ikigai</title><link>https://bongio.me/blog/startup/ikigai/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bongio.me/blog/startup/ikigai/</guid><description>&lt;p>In the last couple of months, I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading and learning about topics I did not care about in the past. If I had heard of them, I would have wondered why people would care about them and believe in them.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A successfull holiday - tips from our trip with our autistic son and neurotypical daugher</title><link>https://bongio.me/blog/autism/autistic_holiday_tips/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bongio.me/blog/autism/autistic_holiday_tips/</guid><description>&lt;p>We spent the half-term break of May 2024 in a holiday village in Belgium, close to where some of our family live.
It was fun! It was enjoyable! It was not as relaxing as a week on the shoreline basking in the sun and a good book, but it was fulfilling and nurturing for our family bonds.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A dad who knows little of his son's autism</title><link>https://bongio.me/blog/autism/a_dad_who_knows_little_of_his_son_s_autism/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bongio.me/blog/autism/a_dad_who_knows_little_of_his_son_s_autism/</guid><description>&lt;p>My son is seven and a half years old. Earlier, I was thinking about what to
write about on this website, and an obvious topic is life as a parent of an
autistic child who has severe learning difficulties.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://bongio.me/about_me/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bongio.me/about_me/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Paolo Ferdinando Bongiovanni. Thanks for visiting!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Be warned, most of what follows has my brand of humour: hard to understand - yeah, I&amp;rsquo;m always puzzled that my jokes fall flat-
and hard to decide if I&amp;rsquo;m being serious or not. If in doubt, I was probably attempting to be facetious.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Cognitive biases, being yourself and fear of biases</title><link>https://bongio.me/blog/biases_and_fear_of_biases/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bongio.me/blog/biases_and_fear_of_biases/</guid><description>&lt;p>A couple of minutes ago, I was thinking about the changes in approach to Mindiply.
These days, I&amp;rsquo;m also listening to the &lt;strong>
 








 

&lt;a href="https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/15798078-decisive">Decisive&lt;/a>&lt;/strong> audiobook by the Heath brothers about cognitive biases and decision-making.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Pushers and pullers - Or how I entrepreneur the wrong way</title><link>https://bongio.me/blog/startup/pushers_and_pullers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bongio.me/blog/startup/pushers_and_pullers/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m an unrelenting pusher. No, not I don&amp;rsquo;t push drugs. I push my products and ideas to people instead
of looking for their pain points and creating solutions to real problems.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>